♪
( birds chirping )
( bell tolls )
( Kirito breathing heavily )
( groans )
JUST TEN MORE MINUTES.
MAYBE FIVE.
Selka: WAKE UP. NOW.
( Kirito groans )
SUGU?
( Selka grunts )
( Kirito gasps )
Selka: WOULD YOU GET UP ALREADY?
IT’S 5:30.
EVEN THOUGH YOU’RE A LOST
CHILD OF VECTA AND A GUEST,
YOU’RE STILL EXPECTED
TO GET UP ON TIME.
Kirito: OKAY.
Selka: HMPH.
♪
( ax chops )
Eugeo: 45!
( ax rings )
Kirito: THERE’S A LOT I DON’T
UNDERSTAND ABOUT THIS PLACE.
BUT I KNOW
I’M GONNA NEED EUGEO’S HELP
TO GET TO CENTORIA.
THING IS, I HAVE TO GET HIM
OUT OF HIS CALLING FIRST,
AND TO DO THAT, WE’LL HAVE
TO CHOP THIS TREE DOWN.
- ( Eugeo sighs ) WHAT WAS THAT?
- Kirito: HUH? OH, NOTHING.
Eugeo: WE’RE ALL DONE
WITH THE MORNING’S QUOTA.
IT’S TIME FOR LUNCH.
Kirito: I’M STARVING.
( winces )
Eugeo: KNOW WHAT I WISH?
I WISH YOU COULD HAVE
TASTED THE PIES ALICE MADE.
THE CRUST WAS SO FLAKY,
AND THERE WAS SO MUCH FILLING.
HAVING IT WITH SOME FRESH MILK
WAS THE BEST.
THERE’S NOTHING IN THE WORLD
THAT TASTED BETTER THAN THAT.
Kirito: WAS THAT
ALICE’S CALLING, A BAKER?
( Eugeo laughs ) NO, NOT EVEN!
BACK IN THOSE DAYS,
SHE WAS STUDYING THE SACRED ARTS
AT THE CHURCH.
SHE WAS THE GREATEST PRODIGY
THIS VILLAGE EVER HAD.
SHE COULD CAST ALL KINDS OF
SPELLS BY THE TIME SHE WAS TEN.
Kirito: WOW.
WHAT’S UP WITH THE GIRL LIVING
AT THE CHURCH, YOU KNOW, SELKA?
Eugeo: OH, SHE’S ALICE’S
LITTLE SISTER.
AFTER ALICE WAS TAKEN AWAY,
SELKA MOVED TO THE CHURCH
TO BECOME A NUN
AND STUDY THE SACRED ARTS.
Kirito: OH.
THERE’S A BUNCH OF KIDS
THERE, TOO.
ARE THEY THERE
FOR THE SAME REASON AS HER?
Eugeo: THEY LOST THEIR PARENTS
TO THE PLAGUE THAT HIT
THE VILLAGE THREE YEARS AGO.
THE CHURCH IS THE ONLY PLACE
THAT HAD ROOM FOR THEM.
POOR KIDS.
IT’S LIKE WE’RE CURSED.
ALL THESE STRANGE THINGS
HAVE BEEN HAPPENING LATELY,
LIKE PEOPLE BEING ATTACKED AND
KIDNAPPED DOWN THE MAIN ROAD.
THE VILLAGERS SAY GOBLINS
ARE THE ONES DOING IT.
Kirito: THERE’S GOBLINS HERE?
Eugeo: I HAVE A FEELING
ALL THAT TALK’S JUST RUMORS.
IF IT WERE TRUE,
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT
SHOULD HAVE COME BY NOW
TO PUT A STOP TO THEM.
THEY’D HAVE
BEEN HERE IN A FLASH,
LIKE WHEN ALICE
TOUCHED THE GROUND
IN THE DARK TERRITORY.
THAT WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO GOBLINS.
Kirito: NO, IT’S NOT.
Eugeo: EITHER WAY,
THERE HAVE BEEN A LOT OF DEATHS
OVER THE PAST TWO OR
THREE YEARS, MORE THAN USUAL.
Kirito: CAN’T YOU REVIVE ’EM?
YOU KNOW, LIKE WITH ONE
OF THE SACRED ARTS?
Eugeo: WELL...
I DON’T KNOW ABOUT THAT,
BUT I REMEMBER ALICE SAYING
THERE WAS
A HIGH-LEVEL SACRED ART
THAT COULD STOP A LIFE
FROM DECREASING.
Kirito: THAT’D BE
A GOOD ONE TO KNOW, I GUESS.
Eugeo: IT WOULD.
ALICE SAID SHE FOUND
A PASSAGE ABOUT THAT SPELL
IN ONE OF THE OLD BOOKS
IN THE CHURCH.
BUT THE PROBLEM IS,
ONLY THE HIGH PRIESTS
AT THE AXIOM CHURCH CAN USE IT.
Kirito: AXIOM CHURCH?
Eugeo: IT’S IN CENTORIA.
THEY WROTE THE TABOO INDEX.
Kirito: BUT, LIKE,
DO YOU HAVE TO BE
A HIGH PRIEST TO USE THE SPELL?
MAYBE SOMEONE LIKE YOU OR ME
COULD LEARN IT.
Eugeo: NO.
IT’S NOT
FOR REGULAR FOLK LIKE US.
THE ARTS GET THEIR STRENGTH
FROM THE SACRED POWER
THAT SOLUS AND TERRARIA
SATURATE THE AIR AND LAND WITH.
THE MORE ELABORATE THE ART,
THE MORE SACRED POWER IT TAKES.
IT WOULD TAKE MORE POWER
THAN THIS FOREST HAS,
AND NO ONE FROM HERE
TO ZAKKARIA COULD WIELD IT.
Kirito: THAT’S TOO BAD.
I WONDER IF THERE’S A SACRED ART
THAT COULD HELP US
TO CHOP THIS THING DOWN.
( Eugeo laughs )
THAT WOULD MAKE THINGS EASIER!
Kirito: THERE’S GOTTA BE
SOMETHING BETTER THAN THIS.
( gasps )
HEY, EUGEO,
IS THERE ANYTHING TOUGHER
THAN THIS IN YOUR VILLAGE?
Eugeo: NO, I’M AFRAID NOT.
THE ONLY THING STRONGER
THAN THE DRAGONBONE AX
WOULD BE AN INTEGRITY KNI--
( sighs )
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
MAYBE THERE IS.
WAIT HERE FOR ME.
I’LL BE BACK IN A BIT.
Kirito: HUH?
♪
( Eugeo panting )
- ( grunts )
- Kirito: WHOA.
YOU OKAY?
( Eugeo panting )
Kirito: MIND IF I OPEN IT?
Eugeo: OKAY. JUST BE CAREFUL.
IF IT FALLS ON YOUR FOOT,
IT’LL LEAVE YOU
WITH MORE THAN A SCRATCH.
( Kirito gasps )
( grunting )
WHEW.
( gasps )
♪
NO WAY.
Eugeo: IT’S THE BLUE ROSE SWORD
FROM THE FAIRY TALE.
Kirito: WHAT FAIRY TALE?
Eugeo: IT GOES LIKE THIS.
300 YEARS AGO,
BERCOULI THE SWORDSMAN
WENT TO THE END MOUNTAINS.
HE ENTERED THE LAIR OF
THE WHITE DRAGON, OUR PROTECTOR,
AND FOUND THAT SWORD.
IT’S JUST A SILLY STORY.
THAT IS, IT WAS,
UNTIL SOME KIDS DECIDED
TO FIND OUT IF IT WAS TRUE.
I MENTIONED IT YESTERDAY.
REMEMBER? ABOUT HOW ALICE AND I
WENT TO THE END MOUNTAINS.
I FOUND THAT SWORD
IN THE DRAGON’S LAIR.
I COULDN’T EVEN LIFT IT
BY MYSELF BACK THEN.
Kirito: REALLY?
WHAT’D THE DRAGON HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT YOU GUYS
BREAKIN’ IN TO ITS HOME?
Eugeo: OH, THERE WAS NOTHING
LEFT OF IT EXCEPT SOME BONES.
WE TOOK THE WRONG TUNNEL,
AND THEN ALICE CROSSED
INTO THE DARK TERRITORY.
AND THEN SHE WAS TAKEN AWAY.
I COULDN’T DO ANYTHING FOR HER,
EXCEPT STAND THERE.
I WANTED TO SAVE HER,
BUT MY ARMS AND LEGS
WERE FROZEN.
I-I’M SORRY. BACK TO THE SWORD.
I LEFT IT THERE THAT DAY
AND NEVER FORGOT IT,
SO TWO SUMMERS AGO,
I WENT BACK.
EVERY DAY OF REST,
I’D GO DRAG IT.
IT TOOK THREE MONTHS
TO GET IT BACK HERE.
Kirito: IT TOOK YOU
THREE WHOLE MONTHS TO DO IT?
WHY’D YOU EVEN BOTHER?
Eugeo: I GUESS I WAS HOPING
ONE DAY I’D HAVE
THE STRENGTH TO SWING IT.
I’M STILL NOT STRONG ENOUGH TO.
DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
Kirito: I’M DOWN TO TRY.
I’M A SWORDSMAN, AFTER ALL.
( hand scraping )
( grunting )
( blade rings )
WHOA! UNH!
( blade clangs )
( sighs )
( Eugeo chuckles )
LOOKS LIKE IT’S
TOO HEAVY FOR YOU, TOO.
( blade rings )
Kirito: IT’S NOT MADE OF STEEL.
OR IS IT?
Eugeo: NO, I DON’T THINK SO.
AND IT’S NOT SILVER
OR DRAGONBONE, EITHER.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE
A DIVINE OBJECT.
Kirito: A WHAT?
Eugeo: IT’S SOMETHING
THAT WAS EITHER MADE
WITH THE HELP OF THE GODS
OR WAS CREATED BY THEM.
WE CALL THINGS LIKE THAT
DIVINE OBJECTS.
Kirito: THAT MAKES SENSE.
HEY, EUGEO? COULD YOU, LIKE,
CHECK HOW MUCH LIFE
THE GIGAS CEDAR HAS NOW?
Eugeo: DON’T TELL ME.
LET ME GUESS.
YOU’RE GOING TO TRY
STRIKING IT WITH THE SWORD.
Kirito:
YOU’RE DAMN STRAIGHT, I AM.
UNLESS THE TABOO INDEX
FORBIDS IT,
BUT I BET IT DOESN’T, DOES IT?
( Eugeo chuckles )
NO, IT DOESN’T.
IT’S FUNNY.
ALL THIS SEEMS SO FAMILIAR.
RIGHT NOW, IT’S AT 232,315.
Kirito: COOL. REMEMBER THAT.
( hands scraping )
( grunts )
( deep breath )
( yells )
( blade rings )
( grunts )
Eugeo: DID YOU HURT YOURSELF?!
Kirito: NO, I’M OKAY.
Eugeo: I TOLD YOU BEFORE.
THAT TREE IS TOUGH.
( gasps )
NO WAY.
YOU ACTUALLY CUT INTO IT.
AND DEEP, TOO.
Kirito: GO ON.
SEE WHERE ITS LIFE’S AT NOW.
Eugeo: OH. RIGHT.
232,314.
Kirito: YOU’RE KIDDING!
IT ONLY WENT DOWN ONE POINT?!
Eugeo: YOUR HIT LANDED
IN THE WRONG SPOT.
I BET IT WOULD HAVE
DECREASED ITS LIFE A LOT MORE
IF YOU GOT IT IN THE CENTER
OF THE CUT INSTEAD OF THE BARK.
LOOKS LIKE
YOUR INTUITION WAS RIGHT.
THE SWORD IS
MORE EFFECTIVE THAN THE AX.
EVEN SO, WE’D HAVE TO MASTER
USING IT TO GET ANY RESULTS.
Kirito: I CAN’T HIT IT STRAIGHT,
BUT I BET YOU COULD.
Eugeo: I CAN BARELY HOLD
THE SWORD, LET ALONE SWING IT.
Kirito: IT’S ALL
ABOUT TECHNIQUE,
AND I CAN HELP YOU WITH THAT.
( Eugeo sighs )
OKAY, I’LL GIVE IT A SHOT.
( grunting )
S-SO HEAVY!
Kirito: FIRST THING,
FIND YOUR BALANCE,
AND WHEN YOU SWING,
SWING WITH YOUR BODY.
WITH SWORDS,
IT’S MORE ABOUT MOMENTUM,
NOT JUST ARM STRENGTH.
Eugeo: MM-HMM.
- ( hands scraping )
- ( deep breath )
Kirito: WHOA!
( blade rings )
( Eugeo grunting )
Kirito: HEY! YOU ALL RIGHT?
Eugeo: I THINK
I LOST SOME LIFE ON THAT ONE.
Kirito: OH, WELL.
IT WAS A GOOD TRY.
( gasps )
IF DURABILITY’S LIFE,
I LOST SOME WHEN I TOOK A SWING.
HMM. IT SAYS MY OBJECT CONTROL
AUTHORITY’S AT 38.
I GUESS THAT’S MY PARAMETER.
THE SWORD’S IS HIGHER.
- ( water splashes )
- ( sighs )
THAT’S WHAT I’M TALKIN’ ABOUT.
( deep breath )
AT THIS RATE,
I’LL NEVER GET TO CENTORIA.
I NEED EUGEO’S HELP, BUT HE
WON’T BAIL ON HIS CALLING.
IF IT WASN’T
FOR THAT TABOO INDEX,
HE COULD DO WHATEVER HE WANTS.
HE SAID THE AXIOM CHURCH
CAME UP WITH IT.
WONDER WHAT THE DEAL IS
WITH THEM.
IF I’M RIGHT AND THESE PEOPLE
ARE A.I. FLUCTLIGHTS
IN A SIMULATED CIVILIZATION,
THERE’S NO WAY THE SYSTEM
WOULD LET ’EM BREAK A RULE.
HANG ON.
EUGEO SAID ALICE
BROKE THE TABOO INDEX
WHEN SHE ACCIDENTALLY
CROSSED INTO THE DARK TERRITORY,
BUT SHE WAS THERE BY CHOICE.
SHE WENT AGAINST THE SYSTEM.
SO IS SHE NOT AN A.I.?
Selka: HELLO?
IS SOMEONE IN THERE?
Kirito: Y-YEAH, THERE IS!
I-I’M ALMOST DONE!
Selka: OH! UM, NO.
YOU CAN TAKE YOUR TIME.
I WAS JUST CHECKING.
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
Kirito: UH, SELKA!
I WANTED TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
Selka: MM...
♪
- ( knock on door )
- MM?
Selka: SO? WHAT WAS IT
YOU WANTED TO ASK ME?
Kirito: YEAH.
UM...
IT’S ABOUT YOUR OLDER SISTER.
( Selka gasps )
Kirito: I HEARD ABOUT HER,
YOU KNOW, FROM EUGEO.
AND, LIKE, HE TOLD ME
HER NAME WAS ALICE.
Selka: HE DID, DID HE?
WHAT ELSE DID HE TELL YOU,
BESIDES HER NAME WAS ALICE?
Kirito: OH, UM,
HE SAID SHE WAS STUDYING
THE SACRED ARTS
HERE AT THE CHURCH
AND HOW, SIX YEARS AGO,
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT TOOK HER.
I GOT THE FEELING
HE’S REALLY WORRIED ABOUT HER.
Selka: I DIDN’T KNOW.
I THOUGHT HE FORGOT ABOUT HER.
THIS EXPLAINS A LOT
ABOUT HIM, THOUGH.
SHE’S THE REASON EUGEO’S SO SAD.
Kirito: I DIDN’T GET THAT.
HE SEEMS FINE.
Selka: HE’S NOT.
YOU HAD TO HAVE NOTICED IT,
HOW QUIET AND GLOOMY HE IS.
Kirito: OH. YEAH.
Selka: WHEN MY SISTER WAS HERE,
EVERY TIME I SAW HIM,
HE HAD A SMILE ON HIS FACE.
I DON’T REMEMBER EVER SEEING HIM
WITHOUT ONE BACK THEN.
BUT NOT ANY MORE. HE SPENDS
HIS DAYS OF REST ALONE,
AND THE ONLY TIME I SEE HIM
IS WHEN HE GOES TO THE FOREST.
Kirito: SELKA...
YOU REALLY LIKE HIM, DON’T YOU?
( Selka squeals )
I DIDN’T SAY THAT! OH, MY GOSH!
( Kirito laughs )
Selka: EVERYONE
COMPARES ME TO ALICE.
NO ONE SAYS IT, BUT I KNOW.
WHEN MY PARENTS SEE ME,
I REMIND THEM OF HER,
AND I CAN’T STAND IT ANY MORE.
THAT’S PROBABLY
WHY EUGEO AVOIDS ME.
WHEN HE SEES ME,
HE THINKS OF HER,
AND I CAN TELL
IT MAKES HIM SAD.
BUT THERE’S NOTHING I CAN DO.
IT’S NOT MY FAULT SHE’S GONE.
( gasps )
I’M SORRY.
I’M ACTING LIKE A BABY.
Kirito: NO, NOT AT ALL.
IT’S GOOD TO CRY.
IT’S BETTER THAN HOLDIN’ IT IN.
Selka: YES, YOU’RE RIGHT.
IN FACT, I FEEL
MUCH BETTER ALREADY.
CRYING IN FRONT OF OTHERS IS...
NOT SOMETHING I DO.
Kirito: REALLY?
YOU’RE TOUGHER THAN I AM.
I CAN’T TELL YOU HOW MANY TIMES
I’VE CRIED IN FRONT OF PEOPLE.
Selka: HOLD ON.
IS YOUR MEMORY BACK?
Kirito: NO! I-IT JUST
FEELS THAT WAY, IS ALL!
A-ANYWAY, BACK TO YOU.
IT DOESN’T MATTER
WHAT ANYONE THINKS.
YOU’RE YOU, NOT YOUR SISTER.
YOU CAN ONLY LIVE YOUR LIFE,
NOT SOMEONE ELSE’S.
( Selka chuckles )
YES, YOU’RE RIGHT.
- ( bell tolling )
- ( gasps )
I SHOULD GET GOING.
SAY...
DID EUGEO HAPPEN TO TELL YOU
WHY THE INTEGRITY KNIGHT
TOOK MY SISTER AWAY?
Kirito: UM, YEAH. HE DID.
Selka: MY PARENTS
WOULDN’T TELL ME,
AND EUGEO
WOULDN’T TELL ME, EITHER.
MAYBE YOU COULD TELL ME WHY?
Kirito: YEAH, SURE.
SHE WENT TO THE END MOUNTAINS,
THEN TOUCHED THE GROUND
ON THE DARK TERRITORY SIDE.
Selka: I SEE.
THE END MOUNTAINS, HUH?
Kirito: UH...
Selka: TOMORROW IS
OUR DAY OF REST.
STILL, BE ON TIME.
I WON’T BE COMING
TO WAKE YOU UP ANY MORE.
Kirito: OKAY.
I’LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
( door closes )
( birds chirping )
( sighs )
Azalia: GOOD MORNING.
Kirito: UH, OH, GOOD MORNING.
Azalia: BY CHANCE,
HAVE YOU SEEN SELKA TODAY?
Kirito: NO.
I JUST WOKE UP, ACTUALLY.
Azalia: SO I SEE. WELL,
I HAVE NOT SEEN HER ALL MORNING.
SHE MISSED PRAYERS,
AND SHE IS NOT IN HER ROOM.
I AM WORRIED. SHE WOULD NEVER
LEAVE WITHOUT TELLING ME FIRST.
Kirito: I’M SURE SHE’S AROUND.
Azalia: I HOPE SO. IF YOU
SEE HER, PLEASE LET ME KNOW.
Kirito: YES, MA’AM.
EUGEO!
Eugeo: HEY, KIRITO.
Kirito: HAVE YOU
SEEN SELKA ANYWHERE?
Eugeo: I HAVEN’T. WHY?
Kirito: SISTER AZALIA’S
BEEN LOOKING FOR HER.
SHE SAYS SHE LEFT
WITHOUT TELLING HER.
Eugeo: THAT’S STRANGE.
Kirito: WELL,
I’M TRYIN’ TO FIND HER.
DO YOU KNOW
WHERE SHE COULD’VE GONE?
Eugeo: NO. SHE AND I
HAVEN’T SPOKEN IN AGES.
DO YOU THINK SOMETHING
MIGHT HAVE UPSET HER?
Kirito: UH...
Selka: I SEE.
THE END MOUNTAINS, HUH?
Kirito: AW, MAN. LAST NIGHT,
I TOLD HER
WHAT HAPPENED TO ALICE,
AT LEAST, EVERYTHING
YOU TOLD ME THAT HAPPENED.
( Eugeo gasps )
Kirito: SHE WOULDN’T GO
TO THE END MOUNTAINS
ON HER OWN, WOULD SHE?
Eugeo: THAT’S EXACTLY
WHERE SHE WENT!
WE HAVE TO BRING HER BACK NOW!
Kirito: WHAT’S WRONG?
Eugeo: IT’S BEEN STEPPED ON.
IT’S LOST A BIT OF LIFE.
SOMEONE’S BEEN BY HERE,
AND IT WASN’T THAT LONG AGO.
Kirito: THEN WE’RE
ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
- THAT’S GOTTA BE SELKA.
- Eugeo: YEAH.
WELL, THIS IS IT.
Kirito: NO WAY.
IT REALLY IS THE END.
Eugeo: WHEN I FIRST CAME HERE,
I THOUGHT THE SAME THING.
Kirito: AND THE DARK TERRITORY’S
DOWN THAT WAY, HUH?
Eugeo: YEAH. ARE YOU READY?
Kirito: YEAH, I THINK. I GUESS.
- Eugeo: SYSTEM CALL.
- ( Kirito gasps )
Eugeo: GENERATE
LUMINOUS ELEMENT.
ADHERE.
Kirito: E-EUGEO! WHAT’D YOU DO?
Eugeo: IT’S A SACRED ART,
AN EASY ONE THAT ANYBODY CAN DO.
Kirito: BUT, LIKE,
YOU SAID, "SYSTEM."
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
Eugeo: NOTHING.
IT’S JUST A WORD,
WELL, A COMMAND.
IT’S TO CALL ON THE GODS.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE
ENOUGH SKILL,
YOU’LL BE BLESSED
WITH THE ART YOU SUMMON.
Kirito: HE THINKS
HE’S CASTING A MAGIC SPELL.
Eugeo: COME ON. LET’S GO.
Kirito: RIGHT.
♪
- ( breeze blowing )
- ( Kirito shivers )
MAYBE SHE DIDN’T COME IN HERE.
I MEAN, THERE’S NO SIGN OF HER.
( Eugeo gasps )
THIS IS AS GOOD A SIGN AS ANY.
Kirito:
IT COULD BE HER, I GUESS.
HEY, EUGEO.
Eugeo: WHAT IS IT?
Kirito: IF SHE CROSSES
INTO THE DARK TERRITORY,
DOES AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT COME
AND TAKE HER RIGHT AWAY?
Eugeo: NO,
NOT UNTIL THE NEXT DAY.
HE’LL FLY TO THE VILLAGE
AND ARREST HER THERE,
JUST LIKE SIX YEARS AGO.
Kirito: THEN,
EVEN IF WE’RE TOO LATE,
WE STILL HAVE A CHANCE
TO KEEP HIM FROM GETTIN’ HER.
( Eugeo sighs )
BUT THAT WOULD BE INTERFERING.
WE CAN’T.
Kirito: OF COURSE WE CAN.
LOOK, EVEN IF SHE DOES
BREAK THE TABOO INDEX,
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
KEEP HER AWAY FROM THE VILLAGE.
THE INTEGRITY KNIGHT
CAN’T ARREST HER
IF HE CAN’T FIND HER.
Eugeo: THAT’S INSANE.
WE CAN’T HIDE FOREVER,
AND I HAVE MY CALLING.
Kirito: BUT I DON’T,
SO I CAN TAKE HER AWAY.
IF I DIDN’T SAY ANYTHING,
SHE WOULDN’T BE IN THIS MESS.
THIS IS ALL ON ME.
Eugeo: NO, IT’S NOT.
( Selka screams )
Eugeo: SELKA!
THAT WAY!
Kirito: TAKE COVER.
( gasps )
( goblins laugh, chatter )
( goblin growls )
Kirito: CRAP. GOBLINS.
( gasps )
( Eugeo gasps )
SELKA!
Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
( goblin growls )
( goblins murmuring )
Goblin #2: LOOKIE, LOOKIE!
TWO MORE WHITE IUM BRATTY-BRATS,
JUST A-WANDERING AROUND!
Goblin #3: YUMMY.
LET’S TIE ’EM TO THE OTHER ONE.
( both laugh )
Goblin #4: SILENCE!
THEY’RE MALE IUMS.
WE TAKE ’EM BACK,
NO ONE BUY ’EM.
WORTHLESS. KILL ’EM,
AND MAKE ’EM MEAT INSTEAD.
( goblins chuckling )
Kirito: EUGEO.
( Eugeo gasping )
Kirito: E-EUGEO?
EUGEO!
( Eugeo continues gasping )
Kirito: EUGEO!
EUGEO!
♪
NEXT TIME: DEPARTURE